nus.edu 2008-06-24

# Privacy Statement: NUS

|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  |  |  |  |  | 

Privacy Statement

National University of Singapore Privacy Statement

  1. This is a National University of Singapore (NUS) website. Thank you for examining our privacy statement. 
  2. The NUS collects personal data to support its teaching, learning, research, administration, personal development and other functions of the University. 
  3. If you are only browsing this website or using the Search function, we do not capture data that allows us to identify you individually. This site automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page(s) requested. Although user sessions are tracked, the users remain anonymous.
  4. If you choose to send an application or an e-mail that contains personally identifiable data, for us to process the application or to render you a service, we may share relevant data within NUS, or if necessary, with other Government agencies, so as to serve you efficiently and effectively, unless such sharing is prohibited by legislation. We may also need to disclose personal data as required by law or a court order. We will NOT share your personal data with non-Government entities, except where such entities have been authorised to carry out specific Government services.
  5. For your convenience, when you are carrying out a transaction using your personally identifiable data, we may also display to you data you had previously supplied to us or to other Government agencies (or non-Government entities that have been authorised to carry out specific Government services). This will speed up the transaction and save you the trouble of repeating previous submissions. Should the data be out-of-date, please supply us the latest data. We will retain your personal data only as necessary for the effective delivery of University services to you.
  6. To safeguard your personal data, all electronic storage and transmission of personal data are secured with appropriate security technologies. 
  7. This site may contain links to other independently-managed websites within the NUS network and to some sites outside the "nus.edu.sg" domain whose data protection and privacy practices may be different from ours. We are not responsible for the content and privacy practices of these other websites and encourage you to examine the privacy notices of those sites.
  8. NUS students may also wish to view the provisions under the '[Privacy Statement for NUS Students](http://www.nus.edu.sg/students/privacy.html)'.
  9. Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal data online – for example on message boards, through e-mails, or in chat areas – that information can be collected and used by others. By posting personal data online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.
  10. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Statement, you should first contact the NUS Quality Manager (email: [qsmanager@nus.edu.sg](mailto:qsmanager@nus.edu.sg)).
  11. The current version of this privacy statement can be found at <http://www.nus.edu.sg/corporate/privacy.htm>.  

back to top

|    
|  |   
|  |   
|   
  
About NUS

Giving to NUS

Campus Map

Job Opportunities

NUS Identity

NUS Structure

Publications

NUS Vision

NUS Mission

NUS Strategy

Facts and Figures

Milestones

Statutes & Regulations

NUS Board of Trustees

NUS Management

University Administration

Faculties and Schools

Research Centres/Institutes

Affiliated Organisations

Annual Reports

Quest for Knowledge

Knowledge Enterprise

Newshub

NUS Video

The AlumNUS

Global Alumni

Global Networking

Global Partnerships

Overseas Colleges

Related Offices

Student Exchange Programme

in Research and Teaching

for Graduate Studies

Silicon Valley

Bio Valley

Shanghai

Stockholm

Bangalore

International Relations

NUS Enterprise

NUS Overseas Colleges

APRU Secretariat

for NUS students

for overseas students

Academic Calendar

Course and Programmes

For Overseas Students

Graduate Studies

Undergraduate Admissions

Student Exchange Programme

Undergraduate Admissions

Non-graduating Programmes

Courses

Financial Aid

How to Apply

FAQs

Scholarships & Awards

Application status enquiry

Academic Calendar

Faculties and Schools

Global Education

Graduate Studies

Language & Communication

NUS Learning Environment

Undergraduate Studies

Student Exchange Programme

For Overseas Students

Awards for Study Abroad

Non-graduating Programmes

NUS College in Silicon Valley

NUS College in Bio Valley

NUS College in Shanghai

NUS College in Stockholm

NUS College in Bangalore

Centre for English Language Communication

Promotion of Standard English

Ctr for Dev of Teaching & Learning

Ctr for Instructional Technology

NUS Libraries

NUS Extension

Online Learning (IVLE)

Self-Access English Learning Facility

General Education

Singapore Studies

Research Centres and Institutes

Research Gallery

Annual Research Report

NUS-affiliated National-level

University-level

Faculty-level

NUS Enterprise

\-----------------------------------

NUS Overseas Colleges

NUS Industry Liaison Office

NUS Entrepreneurship Centre

Business Units

Related Organisations

NUS Extension

NUS Press

NUS Technology Holdings Pte Ltd

Arts and Culture

Sports@NUS

Accommodation

On Campus

Transportation

Student Activities

NUS Communities

Museum

NUS Centre for the Arts

University Cultural Centre

Yong Siew Toh Conservatory

Guest Rooms

Student Accommodation

Visitors' Lodge

Co-operatives

Dining

Health, Wellness & Counselling Centre

Security

Sports and Recreation

Internal Shuttle Bus

Parking in NUS

Clubs and Societies

NUS Students' Union

AlumNet

Campus Sustainability Committee

Clubs and Societies

Halls of Residences

NUS Students' Union

NUS Staff Club

Campus Networking

IT Resources

Student Support

Teaching & Learning

Dial-up Access

Global Roaming Services

NUSNET IV

Virtual Private Network (VPN)

Wireless Computing (WinZone)

Digital Media Centre

IT Security

Notebook & PDA Purchases

Webcasting & Network TV

Supercomputing

Video Conferencing

NUS IT Care

Careers and Employment

Counselling Centre

International Student Services

PC Clusters

Student Affairs

Student Financial Aid

Student Service Centre

Courseware Development

Ctr for Dev of Teaching and Learning

Ctr for Instructional Technology

English Language and Comms

Integrated Virtual Learning

Learning Portal

NUS Libraries

NUS Extension

NUS Teaching Facilities

NUS Publishing

Promotion of Standard English

Self-Access English Learning Facility
